<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<reviews itemIdentifier="MLKDream">
  <review review_id="49720">
    <review_id>49720</review_id>
    <reviewbody>it looks like these files are now off limits. this is very discouraging. if anyone knows how i may obtain this flac, please email me at david [dot] dub [at] gmail [dot] com. thanks!</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Forbidden</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>david.dub</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2005-08-31 21:52:22</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2005-08-31 21:52:22</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>The speach is there, you download the mp3 and you can play it in iTunes!

This is the first time I heard the whole speach... sounds like Dr. King knew he was writing history!</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Still There</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>GodScript</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2008-01-18 02:14:04</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2008-01-18 02:14:04</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>Martin Helped all people stand up. I am gratefull that He lived. He gave us this speach knowing that he was Right, in All that he said. People are hard cases, and he knew it. old prejudice ways were deeply seated in most caucasions. If Martin had been a trouble maker; we would have had more shame and bloodshed. Where are the leaders like him . Where have they all gone to.I am thankfull, though for our President.President Obama, and His Lovely Wife,Our Fist Lady, are Great Leaders.We need more like them. They make all people proud to be living in the USA</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Choose To Stand Up</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>ChooseFreedom</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2009-07-05 18:48:36</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2009-07-05 18:48:36</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>I'm a white woman, age 38. I wish I could have been there, to hear the speech first hand. To join hands with the people there. To be baptized with the hope and inspiration that must have washed over the crowd.

But I listened to the full speech just now, and I know we have failed him. We are still divided on color lines. African Americans still have to suffer hatred, ignorance, racism, distrust, invalidation... lack of equality. We still have racism on both sides and it makes me ashamed and saddened to the point of despair.

I don't know when or if it will ever be fixed... when it will change, be eradicated. Our entire society is built on dualities. It's how we were taught to think. And from the time we're little, somewhere along the way, we learn to mistreat those who are different from us. It hurts me to my soul.

I just wish Dr. King was still here. We still desperately need him. And I'd love to ask his counsel.

Blessings, Peace, and Unity to all,

Holly</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Soulful</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>Anjalena</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2009-09-21 01:26:16</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2009-09-21 01:26:16</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>Americans were so fortunate to have had Dr Martin Luther King.  He stood for everything that was right.  

One cannot listen to this speech and his "I've been to the mountain top" speech and not be moved.</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Excellent</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>skilpad</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2009-10-25 11:34:16</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2009-10-25 11:34:16</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>What nonsense. How can anyone listen to this garbage?</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Nonsense</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>gefiltefist</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2010-02-23 22:30:16</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2010-02-23 22:30:16</createdate>
    <stars>1</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>Obviously racism, ignorance and bigotry are still alive today.

I encourage every parent to download this speech and listen to it as a family on the MLK holiday. 

It doesn't matter what color you are -- this speech can change your life.</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>A speech every American should listen to, again and again</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>Greg479</reviewer>
    <reviewdate>2010-07-15 22:30:26</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2010-07-15 22:30:26</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>We Miss You</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Re: Appreciation Dr.Martin Luther King Jr.</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>E M Hisjsttooreal</reviewer>
    <reviewer_itemname>@e_m_hisjsttooreal</reviewer_itemname>
    <reviewdate>2019-04-04 20:53:27</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2019-04-04 20:53:27</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>He was an inspired man, that speech makes me always doubt of my atheism. And as an Italian man I found embarrassing to compare the stature of a politician like him and the politicians that government my country these days.</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>An embarrassing comparison</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>Paolo Tombolato</reviewer>
    <reviewer_itemname>@paolo_tombolato</reviewer_itemname>
    <reviewdate>2019-09-06 15:27:14</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2019-09-06 15:20:06</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>This is a valuable piece of history. I am glad it has been archived.</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>This is a valuable piece of history.</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>zSarge</reviewer>
    <reviewer_itemname>@zsarge</reviewer_itemname>
    <reviewdate>2019-10-29 02:23:16</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2019-10-29 02:23:16</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>I am so happy to find this audio.  Martin Luther King Jr. was one of the men I look up to in my childhood days. &lt;a href="https://www.jerseywatch.com/features/sports-registration-software" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.jerseywatch.com/features/sports-registration-software&lt;/a&gt;</reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Civil Rights rally</reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>errollweb3248</reviewer>
    <reviewer_itemname>@errollweb3248</reviewer_itemname>
    <reviewdate>2019-11-15 06:11:19</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2019-11-15 06:11:19</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <review>
    <reviewbody>It feels lively to hear the voice of legends! thank you. </reviewbody>
    <reviewtitle>Appreciate!! </reviewtitle>
    <reviewer>kabijwe</reviewer>
    <reviewer_itemname>@kabiwje</reviewer_itemname>
    <reviewdate>2020-01-13 15:21:40</reviewdate>
    <createdate>2020-01-13 15:21:40</createdate>
    <stars>5</stars>
  </review>
  <info>
    <num_reviews>12</num_reviews>
    <avg_rating>4.67</avg_rating>
  </info>
</reviews>
